#### Contact

+33 664988468 (Mobile) ansarisufiyan777@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ ansarisufiyan777 (LinkedIn)

# Top Skills

**JavaScript** 

Python (Programming Language)

React.js

## Languages

Hindi

English

Arabic

#### Certifications

ICT for social impact 2016 Challenge

# Sufiyan Ansari

Senior Full Stack Engineer

Schiltigheim, Grand Est, France

# Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information services industry. Skilled in Databases, HTML, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), Android, and Dropwizard. Strong engineering professional with a Master's Degree focused in Masters in Computer Application from Vivekanand Education Society Institute Of Management Studies and Research.

# Experience

# Gorgias

Senior Full Stack Engineer May 2023 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Paris, Île-de-France, France

At Gorgias, I work as a fullstack engineer, building and scaling features across both backend and frontend.

I collaborate with product and engineering teams to deliver reliable, highquality experiences that empower merchants and improve customer support workflows.

### Leanspace

Frontend Engineer

November 2022 - May 2023 (7 months)

Strasbourg, Grand Est, France

Worked as a senior frontend react engineer on the core product and continued with designing the solution for onboarding customers.

e-bot7 - Al for Customer Service Full Stack Engineer

February 2022 - June 2022 (5 months)

Munich, Bavaria, Germany

Worked on Micro frontend, and Python Serverless framework with AWS cloud platform to achieve the conversational AI bot engine functionality

Colgate-Palmolive

#### **Technical Architect**

September 2021 - February 2022 (6 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Worked on React, and Python to manage the SKU's pricings across 200 countries in the world.

### Visible Alpha

2 years 4 months

### Software Engineer II

April 2020 - September 2021 (1 year 6 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Worked on React & Python to manage the Buy/Sell side entitlements

Dockerised everything into a Linux container.

Celery (RabbitMQ) to process millions of tasks.

Worked on Salesforce data integration with the Insights Product.

Initiated the React Native Mobile App for Insights product

#### Software Engineer I

June 2019 - April 2020 (11 months)

Mumbai Area, India

# **Indus Valley Partners**

Associate Software Engineer

January 2017 - June 2019 (2 years 6 months)

Mumbai Area, India

Automated private equity valuation processes by coding financial models and reports, and developed custom solutions for the alternative asset management industry.

# WealthyFox

Android Developer

October 2016 - December 2016 (3 months)

Mumbai Area, India

Developed an Android app to track analysts' real-time performance, rate them, and enable one-click broker trading.

#### Machadalo

Summer Intern as Android & Front-end Developer

December 2015 - May 2016 (6 months)

Sakivihar Road Powai Mumbai 400086

Built an Android platform for managing hyperlocal advertising inventories and developed the company's portfolio website using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

# Education

Vivekanand Education Society's Institute Of Technology Master's Degree, Masters in Computer Application (2014 - 2017)

Akbar Peerbhoy College of Commerce & Economics Maulana Shaukatali Road Mumbai 400 008

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology · (2011 - 2013)

Maharashtra College of Arts Science and Commerce 246 A Bellasis Road Byculla Mumbai 400 008

HSC, Science · (2009 - 2010)

Allana High School Kurla West SSC